webample.com 2013-04-15

# Web Ample - Privacy Policy

Web Ample is founded on the principles of helping people to discover new information by enabling them to share what they find interesting with one another. Web Ample knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the Web Ample website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy covers Web Ample's treatment of personal information that Web Ample gathers when you are on the Web Ample website and when you use Web Ample services. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Web Ample does not own or control, or to individuals that Web Ample does not employ or manage. 

### Information Collected by Web Ample

We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website, which is to enable users to discover and share information with one another. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with this objective. We collect the following types of information from our Web Ample users: 

  1. Information You Provide to Us:   
We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. 
    * Registration: In order for you to use Web Ample services, such as submitting new links to the website, you must complete a registration form. As part of this registration form, we require select personal information (including your full name, city, state and e-mail address). 
    * User Profile: To allow you to express yourself beyond just the information collected during registration, we enable you to provide additional information, such as a bio, favorite URLs, and instant messaging IDs. In addition, you may choose to include photos of yourself in your profile. As indicated below, in the section titled "Sharing Your Information", you can control how your information is displayed and used. 
  2. Automatic Information:   

    * We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. Web Ample and its authorized agents automatically receive and record certain "traffic data" on their server logs from your browser including your IP address, Web Ample cookie information, and the page you requested. Web Ample uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website. 
    * Web Ample may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page has been viewed. This includes User Profile pages. 
    * Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously. While Web Ample will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available. 

### Children Under 18 Years of Age 

You must be 13 years and older to register to use the Web Ample website. As a result, Web Ample does not specifically collect information about children. If we learn that Web Ample has collected information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. We recommend that minors between the ages of 13 and 18 ask and receive their parents' permission before using Web Ample or sending information about themselves or anyone else over the Internet. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy 

Web Ample may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Web Ample website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.
